Yevhenii Poznii

Python Developer

+38 063 055-29-04

E-mail: epozniy@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/evhenii-poznii/

GitHub: github.com/K1SKEE

Personal summary

Junior Python Developer with 1+ years of practice is seeking to apply and expand my knowledge and skills toward working in a collaborative environment to develop quality software solutions that address and solve business problems, and to grow up as a specialist. I will be a good employee for your team and will not waste your time.

I had a little experience on a volunteer project as a Python developer where I worked with API, DynamoDB, AWS Lambda and serverless framework.

Experience

Podiya, Kyiv - Python Developer

05/2022 - 11/2022

- working as a volunteer;
- · implement REST API;
- implement crawler service for crawling FB posts;
- implement integration tests for REST API using local DynamoDB;
- Tech stack: Python, DynamoDB, AWS lambda, serverless.

NDA, Kyiv - Media Buyer

06/2019 - 09/2020

- work with Facebook ad rooms, generate conversions, run ads, and track traffic;
- targeted Facebook advertising;
- · buying traffic on FB for product offers;
- · optimization and control of advertising campaigns;
- management of advertising budgets.

Pet-projects

Automated Teller Machine:

- Developed a prototype of a real ATM in the console using OOP concepts;
- Developed an ATM prototype using the Django web framework for the backend in Python and simple templates HTML for the UI;
- Developed ATM API using Django REST Framework;
- Developed frontend UI on Javascript and ReactJS and combining it with the ATM API on DRF;
- In the ATM implemented the functionality of opening accounts, and cards in different currencies, replenishing accounts, transferring funds, withdrawing cash, changing PIN codes, transaction history, and automatic conversion of funds when transferring between different currency accounts.

Key skills

Python, Django, Django REST Framework, BeautifulSoup4, aiohttp, aiogram, unittest, JavaScript, ReactJS, HTML5, CSS3, Git, OOP, PostgreSQL, DynamoDB, Docker, Postman

Education

National University of Civil Defense of Ukraine, Kharkiv – master's degree 2018 - 2020

Program Subject Area "Environmental Protection Technologies". Educational Program "Technogenic and Ecological Safety".

National Aviation University, Kyiv - bachelor's degree

2015 - 2018

Faculty of Finance and Entrepreneurship, majoring in Finance and Credit.